YAP SUEN HONG

DATA ANALYST





+65 9169 9621



yapsuenhong15@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/sue n-hong-yap-530b16227/



https://suenhongyap.github.io/

PROFILE

I am a cheerful and responsible individual who has proven to be a leader and a follower. My experiences allowed me to develop the necessary skills to excel in both my studies and work. I am highly motivated and have learnt to strive for success in whatever I do.

SKILLS

- PYTHON
- MACHINE LEARNING
- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- SQL
- TABLEAU
- SPLUNK
- MICROSOFT OFFICE

EXPERIENCE

YISHUN HEALTH

Temporary Staff in the HR Department under HRSS Team
Feb 2023 - Present

- Book pre-employment checkups for staff.
- · Print staff tags for onboarding employees.
- Prepare documents for onboarding staffs to sign,

YISHUN HEALTH

Internship in the HR Department under HRIS Team

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

- Assist in the launching of SAP SuccessFactors.
- Data preparation for data migration from the old system to the new system.
- Create visualization on Tableau to make data analysis more efficient.
- Doing User Acceptance Testing (UAT) test cases for the new system.
- Check whether the data inside the new system matches the data submitted for importing to ensure data integrity and accuracy.
- Create promotional videos to promote SuccessFactors to other employees.

EDUCATION

NANYANG POLYTECHNIC

Diploma in Business Intelligence & Analytics

2020 - 2023

GPA: 3.25

PUNGGOL SECONDARY SCHOOL

2016 - 2019

O-Level Result:

ELR2B2: 16

FISH & CHICKS

Cashier

Dec 2020 - Oct 2021

- · Packing of food.
- Engaging with customers and riders